mcnews.com.au 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy MCNews.com.au

MCNews Privacy Policy

This policy sets out how MCNews and associated websites including, but not limited to mcnews.com.au uses and discloses your personal information.

If you disclose personal information to third parties this policy will not apply and you will be subject to the privacy policy of that third party.  
MCNews will not sell or rent your personal information or share your information in any manner not set out in the following Privacy Policy.

By accessing or using MCNews websites and services you agree to the use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this policy.

Words defined in the MCNews Terms and Conditions of Use have the same meaning in this Privacy Policy.

MCNews is bound by the Privacy Act (1988).

What personal information is collected

MCNews collects personal information that it considers necessary for it, or its related bodies to provide the range of services they offer.

Personal information collected by MCNews may include:  
your name, address and contact details  
bank account and credit account details  
user ID’s and passwords  
the services provided to you  
records of communications with MCNews including records using Communications Services  
How is personal information collected

MCNews collects personal information in a number of ways, including:  
directly from you when you provide information directly to MCNews in person, by phone or in writing ( whether electronic or otherwise)  
directly from you when you communicate with MCNews or any other person using MCNews Services  
from third parties such as:  
MCNews related companies; resellers of MCNews services and service providers to MCNews  
operators of linked or served web sites, applications and advertising on the MCNews websites  
from organisations identified or described under the heading “How is personal information disclosed”  
How is personal information used  
Your personal Information may used for the following purposes:  
to provide the services requested by you  
to manage those services including, customer service and billing  
to research, develop and improve MCNews services  
to conduct surveys to determine use and satisfaction with MCNews services  
to generate statistics in relation to the MCNews services  
to promote and market special offers and other services to you  
MCNews will not sell or rent your personal information  
If you do not want to receive these please let us know by clicking on the “contact us” link at the bottom of this page and advising us that you would like to “opt out”. In addition, if we email you we will include a way for you to “opt out” of receiving further emails.

How is personal information disclosed

MCNews may disclose personal information to individuals and organisations other than MCNews . The organisations to which we may disclose personal information include:  
MCNews and associated websites, its officers, employees, contractors and agents, whether individually or collectively.  
the public if you advertise with its Services or use publicly available Communications Services  
individuals and organisations that advertise with MCNews if you submit an enquiry with MCNews .  
Depending on your enquiry these may include:  
private advertisers  
licensed car dealers  
resellers of MCNews services  
government and regulatory authorities as required by law  
If you do not want MCNews to disclose your personal information to these individuals and organisations do not submit enquires  
How to access your personal information

You generally have a right to access your personal Information. If you wish to access your personal information please contact us.  
Please remember to provide as much detail as you can as this will help us to find the information. There is no charge for this service.

What if you don’t provide personal information?

If you choose not to provide personal information when requested, MCNews may not be able to provide you with the full range of MCNews services.

MCNews , Linked Sites and personal information

When you visit a website or use an application on the MCNews websites, MCNews records anonymous information such as IP address, time, date, referring URL, pages accessed and documents downloaded type of browser and operating system.

Cookies may be used by MCNews to help MCNews provide you with the full range of services it offers, remember your preferences, measure and analyse usage of the MCNews and for security. You may adjust your Internet browser to disable cookies. If you cookies are disabled MCNews may not be able to provide you with the full range of MCNews services.

The MCNews may include links to third party web sites, co branded web sites and applications and advertising served to the MCNews by third parties (Linked Sites). Companies who operate Linked Sites may collect personal Information through the use of cookies and otherwise. MCNews is not responsible for Linked Sites and recommends you read the privacy policy of Linked Sites before disclosing your personal information.

What if I have a problem?

If you have a problem, complaint, want to change your personal information or just wish to enquire about privacy please contact us.

How this policy changes

This policy may change over time. All changes will be published on this website.

About security and personal Information

MCNews takes reasonable steps to protect personal information collected from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modifications or disclosure.
